Caner Bayrambas

Game Developer

0537 599 99 31 ccaner37@hotmail.com linkedin.com/in/canerbayrambas/

ABOUT ME

I've been inside the game industry since 2019. I started with creating game servers and modding games on Steam. After dropping my game servers, I decided to create my own games with Unity Game Engine in December 2020. Games are my permanent passion, I both enjoy creating and playing.

EXPERIENCE

Gambol Games October 2021 - Present

Game Developer

Freelance December 2020 - August 2021

• Developing games on Unity Game Engine

Freelance February 2020 - October 2020

• Managed and created scripts for game servers on Steam

SKILLS & PORTFOLIO

Software Languages	Tools	Languages
C#	Git Version Control	English Advanced
Lua (GLua & FiveM Lua)	Jira, Asana, Bitbucket	Turkish Native
SOLID & OOP	Unity Game Engine	

Portfolio Address

ccaner37.github.io/portfolio

You can see my game's with gameplay videos inside my portfolio. I'm currently working on mobile games.

EDUCATION

Esenyurt Anatolian Highschool - Highschool